psyshop.com 2018-11-12

# Psyshop: Privacy Policy of Psyshop

**Privacy Policy for Psyshop - Version 1.0015 (vom 25th April 2018)**

 *** Introduction**

This privacy policy explains which of your data is collected when using services or calling the websites psyshop.com, psyshop.net, psyshop.at, psyshop.info ('the website'), how this information is used, how it is stored and protected, and to what extent they are exchanged with other websites or companies.

By visiting the website or by using the offers on this website, you declare that you have read, understood and agree to this Privacy Policy. You agree that we store, transmit, and process your data in the European Union. If you do not agree, do not visit or use the website.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time; therefore please check this document before each use of the website, to see if an alteration has taken place.

 *** Type of collected personal data**

'Non-personal data':

If you visit the website, the page views and the IP address assigned by your internet service provider, information about the browser, hardware, and operating system are stored. The storage of this data is carried out by our server hosting provider '1&1 Internet SE, Germany' on the basis of the applicable regulations. This data will be deleted after 6 months. These technical data alone are not enough to identify a person.

'personal data':

We collect, process, and use your personal data without further consent, as far as they are necessary for the contract justification and processing as well as for billing purposes.

If using the services, offers or purchase offers offered on the website, the data required for this process are requested: name, company name, recipient address, billing address and the email address. For payment by credit card or debit card you must also enter the card number, expiry date and additional necessary information.

 *** Cookies**

The websites use cookies that are stored on the user's computer to store settings in the shopping cart and products in the shopping cart.

Only data absolutely necessary for the ordering process are stored in the cookie.

The settings you make in the 'Shopping Cart' (country, currency, shipping method, download format, payment method) as well as the product numbers of the selected products are stored.

You can prohibit cookies in the settings of your browser, but then the website is only partially usable and orders cannot be placed. Please use the help system of your browser to learn how to disable cookies.

 *** Use of third party services**

The website uses third party service providers and websites as part of the fulfillment of a purchase contract. Personal data will be transferred to or from the service providers to perform these services.

\- If paying with PayPal your address for shipment and payment processing information will be transmitted to the Website by PayPal.

To process the PayPal payment, you will be redirected to the website of PayPal where PayPal's privacy policy applies.

\- If using the download option 'Tracks or Zip via Dropbox', the files of the order, as well as the invoice in the form of a PDF file are transferred to the Dropbox cloud.

To download files from Dropbox you will be redirected to the Dropbox website where Dropbox's privacy policy applies.

\- If using the email newsletter, your email address will be transferred to the executing service provider '1&1 Server SE, Germany'.

If you do not want this type of data transfer to take place, you may:

\- Select 'Credit Card' for payment.

\- Execute the downloads directly from the website 'Zip File from Psyshop'.

\- The Email Newslist is optional and you have to register actively.

 *** Use and protection of personal data**

The personal data that you enter, when placing an order, will only be used to fulfill the purchase contract and will be stored within the scope of this fulfillment as well as statutory provisions on accounting, customs clearance and documentation obligations.

Data transfer is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL).

The data are stored in Germany, European Union.

All personal data is stored on a server secured with 'SE Linux' and firewalls, which is restrictedly accessible only to an administrator from the Internet.

We point out that there can be no perfect security, despite all efforts and measures.

 *** Third party links**

The website contains links to third party websites. We are not responsible for the practices or privacy policies of such third party websites. The use of these third party websites is at your own risk. Please, consult the relevant terms and conditions as well as privacy statements of these websites for more information.

 *** Age limit, children's information**

Our websites, products and services are not intended for the collection of personal data from financial transactions with children under 13 years. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it from our files. If parents or guardians find that their under-13-year-olds have provided us with personal data without their consent (or that we have otherwise collected or received such information), they should inform us (see imprint).

If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, or have not reached the age of majority in your country, you must obtain the permission of your parent or guardian before you log in to one or more of the Websites, use a credit card, or provide other information about yourself in the internet.

 *** Information on processed personal data**

The customer has the right to ask us about his stored data and to tell us to delete them.

Please contact us with the subject 'Data Protection Officer' via email to service@psyshop.com or by mail:

Psyshop

Data Protection Officer

Heimbergstr. 11

85250 Altomünster

Germany

 *** E-mail communication**

By entering your email address, when placing an order, you agree that we will send you an email confirming the purchase agreement, including the recipient's address and purchased items, as well as emails about the status of your order or emails with download links of your order.

By subscribing to our mailing list, you agree that we regularly send you emails about new products. You may always delete yourself from the email list. This is possible on our website (https://www.psyshop.com/shop/Info/en/mailinglist.html) or by email (service@psyshop.com).

All product names, logos, and brands are property of their respective owners. All company, product and service names used in this website are for identification purposes only. Use of these names, logos, and brands does not imply endorsement.  
Dropbox is a registered trademark of Dropbox, Inc, US  
PayPal is a registered trademark of PayPal, Inc, US  
All trademarks cited herein are the property of their respective owners.
